<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
 Licensed Materials - Property of IBM

 IBM Sterling Selling and Fullfillment Suite

 (c) Copyright IBM Corp. 2012 All Rights Reserved.

 US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure restricted
 by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
-->
<InputProperties xmlns="http://www.sterlingcommerce.com/documentation/masterInputProperties/input">
    <yfc:doc>
        <Element>
            <Description>
                <div>
					A holder of input properties applicable for the current model. It contains:
					<ol>
                        <li>External properties to be injected into the current model.</li>
                        <li>Properties derived from parent state, based on the input property list defined in the current model. 
						This information is initially captured while punching into the current model from its parent.</li>
                    </ol>
					These input property values are considered while evaluating the rules in the current model. The <code>InputProperties</code>
					element from the output of previous API call should be included in the input for subsequent API call.
				</div>
            </Description>
        </Element>
    </yfc:doc>
    <Property External="" Name="" Path="" Type="" Value="" yfc:DTDOccurrence="ZeroOrMany">
        <yfc:doc>
            <Element>
                <Description>
                    <div>
						This element holds information about input properties for the current model. 
					</div>
                </Description>
            </Element>
            <Attributes>
                <Attribute DataType="Flag" Name="External">
                    <Description>
                        <div>
				  			The flag to indicate whether the property is an external input property or not. If <code>External</code> 
				  			is passed as <b>
                                <code>Y</code>
                            </b>, the property is injected into the model and also captured in the BOM 
				  			under the corresponding <code>LineItem</code>. Default value is <b>
                                <code>N</code>
                            </b>.
					  	</div>
                    </Description>
                </Attribute>
                <Attribute DataType="Text-120" Name="Name">
                    <Description>
                        <div>
							The name of the property in the property pool.
							<code>Name</code> is mandatory, if the property is an external input property.		
						</div>
                    </Description>
                </Attribute>
                <Attribute DataType="Text-480" Name="Path">
                    <Description>
                        <div>
							The path to a property from the property pool.
							<code>Path</code> is mandatory, if the property is an external input property.				
						</div>
                    </Description>
                </Attribute>
                <Attribute DataType="Text-120" Name="Type">
                    <Description>
                        <div>
							The datatype of the property. Valid values: 
							<code>String</code> or <code>Double</code> or <code>Integer</code> or <code>List</code> or <code>Date</code>.
							<code>Type</code> is mandatory, if the property is an external input property.
							<Validation>
                                <Condition>
                                    <code>Type</code> is not valid.</Condition>
                                <Error
                                    Description="Invalid property type was passed in input." ErrorCode="YIC10020"/>
                            </Validation>
                        </div>
                    </Description>
                </Attribute>
                <Attribute DataType="Text-480" Name="Value">
                    <Description>
                        <div>
							The value of the property.				
						</div>
                    </Description>
                </Attribute>
            </Attributes>
        </yfc:doc>
    </Property>
</InputProperties>
