<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
IBM Call Center for Commerce
(C) Copyright IBM Corp. 2013 All Rights Reserved.
US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
-->
<Region Country="" OrganizationCode="" ParentRegionKey="" RegionLevel=""
    RegionSchemaKey="" xmlns="http://www.sterlingcommerce.com/documentation/YCD/getStateRegionList/input">
    <yfc:doc>
        <Element EntityName="Region">
            <Description>
                <div>
	    			In order to retrieve the list of states for a provided country, the following information is required.  Either the RegionSchemaKey to be used or the OrganizationCode for which the YCD_STATE_DROP_DOWN_REGION_SCHEMA rule is defined.  Also Either the ParentRegionKey or the Country to be used to derive the ParentRegionKey for the state. 
	    			<Validation>
                        <Condition>
	    					Either the <code>RegionSchemaKey</code> or the <code>OrganizationCode</code> and <code>ParentRegionKey</code> or <code>Country</code> was not provided.
	    				</Condition>
                        <Error Description="Invalid Input" ErrorCode="?"/>
                    </Validation>
                </div>
            </Description>
        </Element>
        <Attributes>
            <Attribute DataType="String" Name="Country">
                <Description>
                    <div>
						If provided and the <code>ParentRegionKey</code> is not provided, this is used to retrieve the RegionKey of the country in the RegionSchema provided to be used as the ParentRegionKey for determine the list of states.
					</div>
                </Description>
            </Attribute>
            <Attribute DataType="OrgCode" Name="OrganizationCode">
                <Description>
                    <div>
						This is used to determine the <code>RegionSchemaKey</code> defined in <code>YCD_STATE_DROP_DOWN_REGION_SCHEMA</code> if the RegionSchemaKey is not provided.
					</div>
                </Description>
            </Attribute>
            <Attribute Name="ParentRegionKey">
                <Description>
                    <div>
						This region key will be used to derive the list of region's (states or provided region type).
					</div>
                </Description>
            </Attribute>
            <Attribute DataType="String" Name="RegionLevel">
                <Description>
                    <div>
						This attribute is used to define the RegionLevel the user wants to retrieve from the derived region schema.  If this is not provided, the default value is "State".
					</div>
                </Description>
            </Attribute>
            <Attribute Name="RegionSchemaKey">
                <Description>
                    <div>
						This <code>RegionSchemaKey</code> is used to retrieve back both the Country and the RegionLevel which are being requested by this api.
					</div>
                </Description>
            </Attribute>
        </Attributes>
    </yfc:doc>
</Region>
