<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
     IBM Sterling Selling and Fulfillment Suite
     (C) Copyright IBM Corp. 2001, 2013 All Rights Reserved.
     US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
-->
<!-- If CheckIfUserExitIsImplemented="Y" then TransactionId is not REQUIRED -->
<InvokeUE CheckIfUserExitIsImplemented="" DocumentType=""
    EnterpriseCode="" TransactionId="" UserExit="Required" xmlns="http://www.sterlingcommerce.com/documentation/YCP/invokeUE/input">
    <yfc:doc>
        <Element>
            <Description>
                <div>
					This invoke UE wrapper takes a mandatory transaction
					id or document type and a mandatory User Exit name as input. The
					inputs are used to validate the User Exit.
					<br/>
					The input to the UE is passed either as a child
					element or as a text child node of the XMLData
					element.
					<br/>
					This API's entry point to invoking a named UE is to be used
					ONLY for the following :
					<br/>
					1. A UE that takes an Environment and an input XML document pair
					<br/>
					2. A UE which necessarily returns an output XML document
					<br/>
					In cases where the input is as mentioned above but the output is of 
					a datatype that is anything other than an XML Document, an exception will 
					be thrown.
					<Validation>
                        <Condition>If <code>DocumentType</code> and <code>TransactionId</code> are not passed
						</Condition>
                        <Error
                            Description="Either TransactionId or DocumentType is mandatory." ErrorCode="YCP0046"/>
                    </Validation>
                </div>
            </Description>
        </Element>
        <Attributes>
            <Attribute DataType="Flag" Name="CheckIfUserExitIsImplemented">
                <Description>
                    <div> Pass as  <b>
                            <code> Y </code>
                        </b> to only check if User Exit is implemented or not. 
					This flag when passed <b>
                            <code> Y </code>
                        </b> will suppress the invocation of the User Exit. Both <code>TransactionId
					</code> attribute and <code>XMLData</code> element will be ignored and their validation will be suppressed.
					<br/>Default: <b>
                            <code>N</code>
                        </b>
                        <br/>Valid Values: <b>
                            <code>Y</code>
                        </b> or <b>
                            <code>N</code>
                        </b>
                    </div>
                </Description>
            </Attribute>
            <Attribute EntityName="Document_Params" Name="DocumentType" NameInEntity="Document_Type">
                <Description>
                    <div>
						Identifies the document type associated to the
						User Exit.
					</div>
                </Description>
            </Attribute>
            <Attribute EntityName="User_Exit_Impl" Name="EnterpriseCode" NameInEntity="OrgKey">
                <Description>
                    <div>
						If EnterpriseCode is passed, the API uses the User Exit implementation associated with the enterprise. The API evaluates the organization hierarchy of the enterprise to determine which User Exit implementation to use.
					</div>
                </Description>
            </Attribute>
            <Attribute EntityName="Transaction" Name="TransactionId" NameInEntity="Tranid">
                <Description>
                    <div>
						Identifies the transaction associated to the
						User Exit.
					</div>
                </Description>
            </Attribute>
            <Attribute EntityName="User_Exit" Name="UserExit" NameInEntity="UserExitName">
                <Description>
                    <div>
						Name of the User Exit that is to be invoked.
					</div>
                </Description>
            </Attribute>
        </Attributes>
    </yfc:doc>
    <XMLData yfc:AllowAnyElement="skip">PCDATA<yfc:doc>
            <Element>
                <Description>
                    <div>
				The input to the UserExit is passed either as a child element or as
				a text child node of this element. If DTD or XSD validation is required,
				the input must be passed as text.
				<br/>
				Validations will be done to see if the xml is well formed. It is the
				responsibility of the UserExit being called to validate the contents
				of this XML data for functional correctness.
				</div>
                </Description>
            </Element>
        </yfc:doc>
    </XMLData>
</InvokeUE>
