<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- 
Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
IBM Sterling Selling And Fulfillment Suite
(C) Copyright IBM Corp. 2005, 2013 All Rights Reserved.
US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
 -->
<MassManage MassAuditID="" Operation="Required"
    OrganizationCode="Required" SuppressAudit=""
    xmlns="http://www.sterlingcommerce.com/documentation/YPM/massManagePricelistLine/input" yfc:ComplexQuerySupported="Y">
    <yfc:doc>
        <Element>
            <Description>
                <div>The price list line mass manage.
				</div>
            </Description>
        </Element>
        <Attributes>
            <Attribute EntityName="Pricelist_Line" Name="MassAuditID" NameInEntity="Mass_Audit_ID">
                <Description>
                    <div> The unique identifier for the mass audit record. If specified the passed <code>MassAuditID</code> is used else a new one is generated. This is stamped on all the price list lines that got updated as part of this mass manage operation.
					</div>
                </Description>
            </Attribute>
            <Attribute DataType="Action" Name="Operation">
                <Description>
                    <div> Operation to perform
						<br/>Valid Values: 
						<br/>
                        <b>
                            <code>Update</code>
                        </b> - Update the price list lines with values specified in <code>Update</code> element that matches the criteria specified under <code>SearchCriteria</code> element. 
						<br/>
                        <b>
                            <code>Delete</code>
                        </b> - Delete the price list lines that matches the criteria specified under <code>SearchCriteria</code> element. 
						<Validation>
                            <Condition>
                                <code>Operation</code> must be passed in the input.
							</Condition>
                            <Error Description="YCP:Field Mandatory." ErrorCode="YCP0046"/>
                        </Validation>
                    </div>
                </Description>
            </Attribute>
            <Attribute EntityName="Pricelist_Header"
                Name="OrganizationCode" NameInEntity="Organization_Code"/>
            <Attribute DataType="Flag" Name="SuppressAudit">
                <Description>
                    <div> Pass as <b>
                            <code>Y</code>
                        </b> to suppress generation of audits in <code>YFS_AUDIT</code> for price list line mass manage operation.
					<br/>Default: <b>
                            <code>N</code>
                        </b>
                        <br/>Valid Values: <b>
                            <code>Y</code>
                        </b> or <b>
                            <code>N</code>
                        </b>
                    </div>
                </Description>
            </Attribute>
        </Attributes>
    </yfc:doc>
    <SearchCriteria>
        <yfc:doc>
            <Element>
                <Description>
                    <div>Search criteria for the mass manage operation, If not specified the mass manage operation is applicable to all price list lines for the <code>OrganziationCode</code>.
					</div>
                </Description>
            </Element>
        </yfc:doc>
        <PricelistLine EndDateActive="" FromQuantity=""
            HasItemAttributes="" ItemID="" PriceTypeName=""
            PricingStatus="" StartDateActive="" ToQuantity="" UnitOfMeasure="">
            <yfc:doc>
                <Attributes>
                    <Attribute Name="HasItemAttributes">
                        <Description>
                            <div>
                                <br>This field is a boolean.</br>
                                <br>If HasItemAttributes is Yes and AttributeBasedPricing rule is Yes then PricelistlineAttr records are removed when PricelistLine is deleted.</br>
                                <br>If HasItemAttributes is Yes and AttributeBasedPricing rule is No then exception is thrown.</br>
                                <br>If HasItemAttributes is No and AttributeBasedPricing rule is Yes then only PricelistLine records are removed(there wont 	be any PricelistLineAttr records).</br>
                                <br>If HasItemAttributes is No and AttributeBasedPricing rule is No then only PricelistLine records are removed.</br>
                            </div>
                        </Description>
                    </Attribute>
                </Attributes>
            </yfc:doc>
            <Item>
                <yfc:includeInParent IncludeXMLChildNodes="Y"
                    IncludeXMLFileName="YPM_Item_master.xml" IncludeXMLPath="/Item"/>
                <yfc:doc>
                    <Element EntityName="Item_Vw">
                        <Description>
                            <div>The view is a subset of YFS_ITEM table. Passing this element results in check for existense of item in catalog.</div>
                        </Description>
                    </Element>
                </yfc:doc>
                <PrimaryInformation ShortDescription=""/>
                <CategoryFilter CategoryPath="">
                    <yfc:doc>
                        <Element EntityName="Category_Item_Vw">
                            <Description>Used to filter items based on category. This element is not enabled for complex query.</Description>
                        </Element>
                    </yfc:doc>
                </CategoryFilter>
            </Item>
            <PricelistHeader AbsoluteAdjustmentOverride="" Currency=""
                Description="" EndDateActive=""
                InheritFromPricelistHeaderKey="" MarkedForListPrice=""
                PercentAdjustmentOverride="" PricelistHeaderKey=""
                PricelistName="" PricingStatus="" StartDateActive="">
                <yfc:includeInParent IncludeXMLChildNodes="Y"
                    IncludeXMLFileName="YPM_Pricelist_Header_master_noOrgCode.xml" IncludeXMLPath="/PricelistHeader"/>
                <yfc:doc>
                    <Element EntityName="Pricelist_Header"/>
                </yfc:doc>
            </PricelistHeader>
        </PricelistLine>
    </SearchCriteria>
    <PricelistLineUpdate AbsoluteAdjustment=""
        AbsoluteAdjustmentUpdType="" ListPrice="" ListPriceUpdType=""
        PercentAdjustment="" PercentAdjustmentUpdType="" PricingStatus="">
        <yfc:doc>
            <Element>
                <Description>
                    <div>Contains the attributes on the price list line to update. Required if the mass manage <code>Operation</code> is <b>
                            <code>Update</code>
                        </b>. This update is applied to all the price list lines that matches the price list line search criteria specified under the <code>SearchCriteria</code> element.
					</div>
                </Description>
            </Element>
            <Attributes>
                <Attribute EntityName="Pricelist_Line"
                    Name="AbsoluteAdjustment" NameInEntity="Absolute_Adjustment">
                    <Description>
                        <div> Absolute uplift or discount on the <code>ListPrice</code>. Value is used in conjunction with <code>AbsoluteAdjustmentUpdType</code>.</div>
                    </Description>
                </Attribute>
                <Attribute DataType="Action" Name="AbsoluteAdjustmentUpdType">
                    <Description>
                        <div> The type of update to perform. No updates happen if <code>AbsoluteAdjustment</code> attribute is void. If <code>AbsoluteAdjustmentUpdType</code> attribute is not passed or if it is void then the value specified in the <code>AbsoluteAdjustment</code> attribute is used for update, the value in the <code>AbsoluteAdjustment</code> replaces the existing value of the price list line.
							<br/>Valid Values: 
							<br/>
                            <b>
                                <code>PERCENT</code>
                            </b> - <code>AbsoluteAdjustment</code> of price list line is updated by a percentage value specified in <code>AbsoluteAdjustment</code> attribute. 
							<br/>
                            <b>
                                <code>ADD</code>
                            </b> - <code>AbsoluteAdjustment</code> of price list line is updated by adding the value specified in <code>AbsoluteAdjustment</code> attribute.
							<br/>None - Value in the <code>AbsoluteAdjustment</code> attribute itself is used for update. No updates happen if <code>AbsoluteAdjustment</code> attribute is void.     
						</div>
                    </Description>
                </Attribute>
                <Attribute EntityName="Pricelist_Line" Name="ListPrice" NameInEntity="List_Price">
                    <Description>
                        <div> List Price of an item. Value is used in conjunction with <code>ListPriceUpdType</code>. API ensures that the least value of <code>ListPrice</code> on the price list lines after all updates is zero.</div>
                    </Description>
                </Attribute>
                <Attribute DataType="Action" Name="ListPriceUpdType">
                    <Description>
                        <div> The type of update to perform. No updates happen if <code>ListPrice</code> attribute is void. If <code>ListPriceUpdType</code> attribute is not passed or if it is void then the value specified in the <code>ListPrice</code> attribute is used for update, the value in the <code>ListPrice</code> replaces the existing value of the price list line. API ensures that the least value of <code>ListPrice</code> on the price list lines after all updates is zero.
							<br/>Valid Values: 
							<br/>
                            <b>
                                <code>PERCENT</code>
                            </b> - <code>ListPrice</code> of price list line is updated by a percentage value specified in <code>ListPrice</code> attribute. 
							<br/>
                            <b>
                                <code>ADD</code>
                            </b> - <code>ListPrice</code> of price list line is updated by adding the value specified in <code>ListPrice</code> attribute.
						</div>
                    </Description>
                </Attribute>
                <Attribute EntityName="Pricelist_Line"
                    Name="PercentAdjustment" NameInEntity="Percent_Adjustment">
                    <Description>
                        <div> Percent uplift or discount on the <code>ListPrice</code>. Value is used in conjunction with <code>PercentAdjustmentUpdType</code>.</div>
                    </Description>
                </Attribute>
                <Attribute DataType="Action" Name="PercentAdjustmentUpdType">
                    <Description>
                        <div> The type of update to perform. No updates happen if <code>PercentAdjustment</code> attribute is void. If <code>PercentAdjustmentUpdType</code> attribute is not passed or if it is void then the value specified in the <code>PercentAdjustment</code> attribute is used for update, the value in the <code>PercentAdjustment</code> replaces the existing value of the price list line.
							<br/>Valid Values: 
							<br/>
                            <b>
                                <code>PERCENT</code>
                            </b> - <code>PercentAdjustment</code> of price list line is updated by a percentage value specified in <code>PercentAdjustment</code> attribute. 
							<br/>
                            <b>
                                <code>ADD</code>
                            </b> - <code>PercentAdjustment</code> of price list line is updated by adding the value specified in <code>PercentAdjustment</code> attribute.
							<br/>None - Value in the <code>PercentAdjustment</code> attribute itself is used for update. No updates happen if <code>PercentAdjustment</code> attribute is void.     
						</div>
                    </Description>
                </Attribute>
                <Attribute EntityName="Pricelist_Line"
                    Name="PricingStatus" NameInEntity="Pricing_Status">
                    <Description>
                        <div>Status of the price list line. No <code>PricingStatus</code> updates happen if this attribute is void.
							<Validation>
                                <Condition>Passed <code>PricingStatus</code> is not a valid value.</Condition>
                                <Error
                                    Description="Invalid PricingStatus." ErrorCode="YPM10012"/>
                            </Validation>
                        </div>
                    </Description>
                </Attribute>
            </Attributes>
        </yfc:doc>
    </PricelistLineUpdate>
</MassManage>
